MARY LE

A product designer with a solid background in UX research, UI design, and frontend development.

EDUCATION

Cornell University | Ithaca, NY

Masters in Information Science | Expected May 2018

University of California, Irvine | Irvine, CA

Bachelor of Arts in International Studies & Sociology | June 2011

EXPERIENCE

Mareana | Princeton, NJ

Student UX Designer | Spring 2018

• Created an interactive tutorial for HR professionals as an onboarding aid for new users.

Cornell Johnson Graduate School of Management | Ithaca, NY

Web Developer Assistant | 09.2017 - Present

• Conduct interviews for user research, A/B test website designs, and produce high-quality content images for the web.

Northwestern Polytechnic University | Fremont, CA

Front-end Developer | 04.2016 - 07.2017

• Created user-centered design wireframes, rapid prototyped with HTML and CSS, led and ran usability testing for school website.

Mobile Action | San Francisco, CA

Front-end Web Developer | 05.2015 - 12.2015

- Prototyped UI designs and developed the frontend for projects.
- · Collaborated with PMs and stakeholders to design products.

Achievers | San Francisco, CA

Front-end Web Developer | 04.2015 - 07.2015

- Rapid prototyped with HTML, CSS, and Javascript (Angular.js) to build a mobile survey application.
- Collaborated with designers on a corporate website relaunch.

ABOUT ME

Portfolio: http://maryle.me

Ithaca, NY maaaryle@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/maaaryle

SKILLS & TOOLS

UX Research

1:1 interviews, affinity diagrams, personas, heuristic evaluation, usability testing, journey mapping, user-centered design methods, prototyping

UI Design

Adobe Photoshop/ Illustrator/InDesign, InVision, Sketch, Balsamiq

Development

HTML, CSS (Sass, LESS, Bootstrap), Javascript (jQuery), C++, Java, Unity 3D, MEAN Stack, Git, Heroku, WordPress, Drupal